welcome back to another audacity
欢迎回到另一个大胆的地方
tutorial in this video I'm gonna show
在这段视频中 我将展示教程
you how you can grab the audio portion
你可以如何抓取音频部分
of a movie or video file using audacity
使用Audacity创建电影或视频文件的
so I have this video here
所以我这里有一段视频
it's just when we grabbed off at pixabay
就在我们抓到Pixabay的时候
it has some rain falling on a window and
一些雨落在窗户上
it just sounds like this so let's say I
只是听起来是这样的 所以我们假设我
want to just make an edit to the audio
我只想对音频进行编辑
portion of this video so we can actually
视频的一部分 所以我们实际上可以
just take it left click and drag this
只要拿着它 左键点击并拖动这个
video on to audacity and it will bring
将视频上传到Audity 它将带来
in just the audio this is really cool
在音频中 这真的很酷
so a couple about a month ago actually I
所以大约一个月前 实际上我
had a client to send me a video that he
有一个客户给我发了一段视频 他说
was having trouble syncing so he had
在同步方面有困难 所以他有
recorded it on his iPhone and by the it
录制在他的iPhone上 并被它
was like an hour long or a 30 minute
就像一小时或三十分钟
long presentation and by the end of it
冗长的演讲 并在结束时
his audio was off by like 2 or 3 seconds
他的音频中断了大约2到3秒
and so I was able to fix it using
所以我能够用它来修复它
audacity I just did brought the video in
我刚刚大胆地把视频带进来了
just like this and got the audio portion
就像这样 并得到了音频部分
of it and then I adjusted it in audacity
然后我大胆地调整了一下
by 2 seconds I just lengthened it out
我把它延长了2秒
and then made sure the pitch and
然后确保投球和投球
everything was the same and then I used
一切都一样 然后我用
kdenlive to put the video back together
Kdenlive将把视频重新组合在一起
and so that's a kind of a practical use
所以这是一种实际的用途
of this but anyway maybe we want to get
但不管怎样 也许我们想要
just this rain sound so we could now
只有这雨声 所以我们现在可以
just go file export as mp3 or WAV and
只需将文件导出为mp3或wav 然后
then we have the audio of this maybe
然后我们就能听到这个的声音了
it's a music video but we just want to
这是一段音乐录像带 但我们只想
listen to the music on our mp3 player so
听我们mp3播放器上的音乐吧
we could just do it as simple as that or
我们可以就这么简单地做 或者
we can take and we only want to use like
我们可以使用 我们只想像这样使用
a portion of the audio so we can select
音频的一部分 以便我们可以选择
a certain portion clip everything else
一定的一部分把其他的都剪掉
outside of that make sure we set it to
除此之外 请确保我们将其设置为
the our beginning here and then we have
我们从这里开始 然后我们有
just a small little sample of rain
只有一小点雨
this rain and thunder sound so that's
这雨声和雷声 所以那是
really it
真的吗？
I guess since this video is super short
我猜因为这个视频很短
I'll talk a little about exporting since
我将谈一谈出口 因为
I kind of you know gone through that
我想你也知道 我经历过
quickly in past videos so one thing
在过去的视频中快速播放一件事
about audacity is if we go to save if we
关于胆量是如果我们去储蓄 如果我们
just save project it's gonna bring up
省省它会带来的项目吧
this warning dialog box and say hey just
此警告对话框并说嘿Just
so you know if you save it's not going
所以你知道如果你救了它就不会
to save on sound file it's gonna save an
为了保存声音文件 它将保存一个
audacity project file so we came back
Audacity项目文件 所以我们回来了
okay that's fine so if we save this on
好的 那很好 所以如果我们把这个留在
our desktop and hit save this file looks
我们的桌面和点击保存此文件看起来
like this it's a folder with just like
就像这样 它是一个文件夹 就像
some weird folders and weird things in
里面有一些奇怪的文件夹和奇怪的东西
it so this is not dasa T file and then
所以这不是DASA T文件 然后
when we go to if we close out of
当我们去如果我们关闭的时候
audacity and then we get back into
大胆 然后我们又回到
audacity well actually this is that this
厚颜无耻其实这就是这
is a file but this is associated with it
是一个文件 但这与其相关联
but so if we go to open it up we go to
但如果我们去打开它 我们就会去
open and we go desktop then we can
打开我们的桌面 然后我们就可以
actually open this project right here
实际上就在这里打开这个项目
called run off so we can open this and
叫Run Off这样我们就可以打开这个
see it but if we want to save just the
请看 但如果我们只想保存
audio portion like export the audio to
音频部分 如将音频导出到
use in a video project or to have an mp3
在视频项目中使用或拥有mp3
to listen to we can go export export as
要听 我们可以出口出口为
WAV and then we can export to the
WAV 然后我们可以导出到
desktop so save and now it's an actual
所以保存桌面 现在它是一个实际的
WAV file as well so I'm gonna delete
Wav文件也是如此 所以我要删除
this bit of clothes out of it first I'm
先把这点衣服脱下来 我是
gonna delete this and now we have just a
我要删除它 现在我们只有一个
WAV file we can listen to of just that
我们可以收听到的WAV文件
portion that we edited one thing I
我们编辑的部分有一件事是
forgot to say you have to have ffmpeg
忘了说你必须要有ffmpeg
installed ffmpeg is like a free
安装的ffmpeg就像是免费的
open-source software for video and audio
视频和音频的开源软件
processing and I don't think it comes by
处理过程中 我不认为它来自
default with audacity I'm pretty sure
默认大胆 我很确定
the first time I did it when I tried to
我第一次这样做的时候 我试图
drag and drop a video in it said you
拖放一段视频 上面说你
don't have ffmpeg do you want to
没有ffmpeg 你想要吗？
automatically download it I just clicked
自动下载我刚刚点击了
yes and it did that so if that dialog
是的 它做到了 所以如果那个对话
box comes up for you when you're trying
当你尝试的时候 盒子就会出现
to do this on Windows you can go ahead
要在Windows上执行此操作 您可以继续
and do that you can also download ffmpeg
然后你也可以下载ffmpeg
just do a Google search or maybe I'll
在谷歌上搜索一下 要不我就
make a video of it but search audacity
把它拍下来 但要大胆地搜索
install SSM peg if you do a google
如果您使用Google 请安装SSM peg
search for that you'll find a tutorial
搜索它 你会找到一个教程
showing you how to do that but you do
教你如何做到这一点 但你做到了
have to have ffmpeg and I'm trying to
必须有ffmpeg 我正在努力
think here I don't know if I if I can
想着这里 我不知道我是否可以
actually testing I don't know if I can
实际上我不知道我能不能
export mp3s
导出MP3
maybe I can no see ya so I also don't
也许我看不到你 所以我也看不到
have a lame properly installed so let me
正确地安装了一个跛子 所以让我
make a video on that showing how to get
在上面制作一段视频 展示如何获得
lanes configured and ffmpeg configured
配置了车道并配置了ffmpeg
for you because you can't export oh here
给你的 因为你不能出口哦这里
we go right here just click download
我们只需点击下载即可进入此处
maybe it'll just do it or maybe it'll
也许它就这么做了 或者它会
take us to the page anyway you can go
把我们带到页面 无论如何你都可以去
you can just walk through these steps
你可以走完这些步骤
here and it tells you how to do it but
在这里 它告诉你怎么做 但是
I'll make a video kind of walking
我会拍一段走路的视频
through it as well because you have to
也经历过因为你必须
have in order to export your mp3s you'll
为了导出您的mp3 您需要
have to have that what else when we
必须要有那个 还有什么当我们
export OGG is that can open source audio
导出Ogg是可以开源的音频
format so that's a cool one you can
格式 所以这是一个很酷的 你可以
export in you can export as MIDI but
导出到您可以导出为MIDI 但是
that's only gonna be if you actually
只有当你真的
have a MIDI sequence export audio lets
有一个MIDI序列导出音频文件
us just choose oh cool so if you want to
我们只要选择哦 酷 所以如果你想
export in a different version you can
可以导出为不同的版本
just go export audio then you can choose
只要去导出音频 然后你就可以选择
from this drop-down so if you want to do
从这个下拉列表中 所以如果您想要
like this FLAC is like a lossless really
就像这样 FLAC就像一个真正的无损
good like audio format there's always
很好的音频格式总是有的
there's like different file different
就像不同的文件不同
formats as well but and if it says
格式也是如此 但是如果它说
ffmpeg after it then you have to have
在它之后 你必须要有
ffmpeg installed in order to do these
安装ffmpeg以便执行这些操作
like these are more like video like
像这些更像是视频
formats that like this AAC is an audio
像这样的AAC格式是一个音频
type that gets used in video quite often
视频中经常使用的类型
so but that's how you would save
所以这就是你省下的钱
something other than these ones that it
除了这些以外的其他东西 它
just gives you by default these three so
默认情况下会给您这三个选项
that turned into a kind of more of a
这变成了一种更多的
video than just importing audio tracks
视频 而不仅仅是导入音轨
from a video but hopefully you found
但希望你能找到
that informative and I'll catch you on
这很有启发意义 我会跟你说的
the next video
下一个视频